AIMANE ELOUAZZANI

Product / UX Designer Developer Safi - Morocco

Experiences

UX Design Generalist - Freelancer

Mar 2015 - Present

My role depends on the client's project which generally revolves around:

- Leading the design process to build and deliver a wide range of deliverables
- Performing user experience research and empathizing with the users
- Producing Design Systems and UI elements.
- Working with developers on the design integrations, design specifications, data and information architecture
- Exploring alternative solutions for constraints and keeping the team focused on the users needs

UX/UI Designer - Contractor | UM6P

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

Worked as a UX/UI Designer in the "SEP Project" for the UM6P and OCP Foundation, to create a platform that helps young students and graduates in Africa strengthen their skills and leadership by offering them guidance, mentorship, knowledge and broadening their opportunities

Education

3 years - Software Engineering

Jan 2019 - Oct 2021

1337 Khouribga - 42 Network

Specialised Technician in Information Technology

Sept 2016 - July 2018

Specialised Institut of Applied Technology - TAZA

Certifications

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

Oct 2021 -- Google | Coursera

Technical Support Fundamentals

Sep 2020 -- Google | Coursera

Operating Systems

Sep 2020 -- Google | Coursera

Android Developer

Apr 2018 -- Udacity | OMAC Dubai



@ aymane2020@gmail.com

in aelouazz

aelouazz

About

As a designer with a background in IT, I was first drawn to UX by the way it combines empathy and creativity. It excites me to build a solution that users can interact with and find useful.

My strengths include building products that are accessible and

Skills

universal.

- User Research
- Graphic Design & Illustration
- Personas & User Flows
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Information Architecture
- Data Modeling
- 3d Modeling & Rendering
- Low Level Programming
- Front End Development

Tools

Adobe Creative Suite Figma				
Miro	Trello	Unix	Terminal	
Sketchbook Pro Git			CSS	
HTML	Javas	Javascript Clang		
Blender 3D .Net Framwork				
Android Studio IT Networks				
UML	Can	va	Krita	
Design	n System:	s W	CAG 2.2	